<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Demo</string>

    <string name="large_text">
        "H. Tao and C. Adams.\n"
        "Pass-Go: A Proposal to Improve the Usability of Graphical Passwords.\n"
        "Int. J. Network Security, 7(2):273–292, 2008.\n\n"

        "   Inspired by an old Chinese game, Go, we have designed a new graphical password scheme, Pass-Go, in which a user selects intersections on a grid as a way to input a password."
        "While offering an extremely large full password space (256 bits for the most basic scheme), \n"
        "our scheme provides acceptable usability, as empirically demonstrated by, to the best of our knowledge, the largest user study (167 subjects involved) on graphical passwords,"
        "conducted in the fall semester of 2005 in two university classes.\n\n"
        "   Our scheme supports most application environments and input devices, rather than being limited to small mobile devices (PDAs), and can be used to derive cryptographic keys."

        "We study the memorable password space and show the potential power of this scheme by exploring further improvements and variation mechanisms.\n\n"

        "Read more \n"
        "http://passgo.ca/ijns-2008-v7-n2-p273-292.pdf"
    </string>


    <!-- general-purpose Strings -->
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="btn_create_password">Create password</string>
    <string name="btn_enter_password">Enter password</string>
    <string name="btn_ok">OK</string>
    <string name="btn_yes">Yes</string>
    <string name="btn_no">No</string>
    <string name="btn_done">Done</string>
    <string name="btn_clearall">Clear all</string>
    <string name="btn_undo">Undo</string>
    <string name="msg_pw_correct">Password correct!</string>
    <string name="msg_pw_wrong">Wrong password!</string>
    <string name="label_input">Input:</string>
    <string name="label_round">Round</string>

    <!-- Open Pass-Go Strings -->
    <string name="title_activity_pass_go">Open Pass-Go</string>
    <string name="title_activity_pass_go_create_password">Open Pass-Go: Create Password</string>
    <string name="title_activity_pass_go_login">Open Pass-Go: Enter Password</string>
    <string name="title_dialog_pass_go_createpw">Select pattern</string>
    <string name="msg_dialog_pass_go_createpw">Please draw your desired pattern in the designated grid.\nYour pattern has to contain %d line segments and / or dots.</string>
    <string name="msg_dialog_pass_go_deletepattern">Would you really like to delete the pattern?</string>
    <string name="title_dialog_pass_go_rememberpw">Please memorize the pattern:</string>

    <!-- Papers -->
    <string name="paper_check_out">Check out our paper:</string>
    <string name="paper_references">This implementation is based on:</string>
    <string name="paper_pass_go">H. Tao and C. Adams. Pass-Go: A Proposal to Improve the Usability of Graphical Passwords. <i>Int. J. Network Security</i>, 7(2):273–292, 2008.</string>
    <string name="paper_tapi">J. Citty and D. R. Hutchings. TAPI: touch&#8211;screen authentication using partitioned images. Tech. Report 2010&#8211;1, Elon University, 2010.</string>
    <string name="paper_uyi">E. Hayashi, R. Dhamija, N. Christin, and A. Perrig. Use Your Illusion: secure authentication usable anywhere. In <i>Proc. SOUPS \'08</i>. ACM, 2008.</string>
    <string name="paper_miba">D. Ritter, F. Schaub, M. Walch, and M. Weber. MIBA: Multitouch image-based authentication on smartphones. In <i>Proc. CHI \'13 Extended Abstracts</i>. ACM, 2013.</string>
    <string name="paper_exploring_designspace">F. Schaub, M. Walch, B. Könings, and M. Weber. Exploring the design space of graphical passwords on smartphones. In <i>Proc. SOUPS \'13</i>. ACM, 2013.</string>


</resources>
